







Summary

Jump to Section

A competent professional with over 4 years of experience in IT Project Management, Software Development, Software Design, Requirement Gathering, XML, Eclipse, SQL Server, Javascript, Bootstrap, JDBC, Maven, Hibernate, jQuery

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Work Experience

Capgemini as Associate consultant-Java developer Jun 2019 to Till Date

java developer with knowledge in front end technologies

Cognizant technology solutions as Programmer Analyst Feb 2016 to May 2019

Program analyst

Java developer with other Frontend and DB knowledge

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Instrumentation) from RMK Engineering College, Chennai in 2015

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Core Java, spring , spring boot	
hibernate,Splunk ,Unix	
HTML5, CSS3, bootstrap 4,java script,	
JQUERY	
SQL, xquery,xpath ,XML	

^ Back to Top

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
tamil				
Telugu				

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Synchrony Financial Client: Synchrony Financial Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Programmer

Duration: Jun 2019 - Aug 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 5

Skill Used: java

Role Description: developer
Project Details: Synchrony is a banking application that allows users to pay their credit card bills. I was a part of the application team and we predominantly worked on java spring and other front end technologies.

Project Title: Lexis Nexis Client: LexisNexis Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Chennai Role: Programmer

Duration: Jul 2016 - May 2019 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 6

Skill Used: java xquery SQL Role Description: developer

Project Details: I was a backend developer at lexis nexis . lexis nexis is a digital library for legal documents and our part was handling the search engine part of the application.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

 ${\it Careers-About\,Us-Clients-Terms\,\&\,Conditions-FAQ's-Contact\,Us-Report\,a\,Problem-Site\,Map-Resources}$ Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.